auron responds to gemita I'm glad you
auron responde a gemita me alegro que
admitted the facts obviously
haya reconocido los hechos obviamente
after that I wasn't going to go and
después de eso no iba a ponerme a
give her a bouquet of flowers let's
regalarle un ramo de flores vamos a
listen yesterday I saw gema's live eh
esuchar ayer vi el directo de gema eh
wow very well to open up and admit well
ostia muy bien el abrir y admitir pues
all those things The truth is well then the
todas esas cosas La verdad bien luego la
second point I want to make
segunda puntualización que quiero hacer
is about the anger let's see Well I think it
es lo del enfado a ver Bueno yo creo que
's understandable No, well of course you're not going to
es comprensible No pues claro no vas a
react in the best way No, of course you're
reaccionar de la mejor manera No claro
not going to give her a hug or
no le vas a dar un abrazo ni le vas a
give her a bouquet of flowers you're not going to
regalar un ramo de flores no te vas a
curse the [ __ ] who gave birth to you and more
[__] en la [__] que te parió y más
taking into account that this is
teniendo en cuenta que esto es un dato
important information that we were a week and a
importante que estábamos a una semana y
half away from moving in together so of
media de irnos a vivir juntos con lo
course how how how you Imagine
cual claro cómo cómo cómo tú Imagínate
the situation of being about to go
la situación de estar a punto de irte a
live with someone a week and a half away and
vivir con alguien a una semana y media y
everything explodes in your personal life, well thank goodness she
que estalle todo en tu vida personal
found out No, well at
pues menos mal no que se enteró No pues
least thank goodness because if you get to
menos menos mal porque si se llega Ah a
live Well of course I understand that she
vivir Bueno claro entiendo que ella se
would have gone There, not to auron's house,
hubiese ido Ahí no a casa de auron no se
she wouldn't have gone into auron's house  I
hubiera metido ella en casa de auron que
think it's big. Well, he would have gotten
creo que es grande Eh pues se hubiera
in there and he would have found out while he
metido ahí y y se Hubiera enterado
was inside the house about the whole
estando dentro de la casa ha todo el
panorama. That guy, the little gem, he has
panorama ese vayate la la gemita eh ha
exceeded several expectations.
superado varias expectativas